# **DeAngelo Wilson**

Evansville, IN deangelowilson12@gmail.com - 3177488075

Experienced Glazer some skills in Carpentry, Painting and Drywall hanging. Recognized for ability to work effectively with a team or alone. Dedicated worker with strong time management and organizational skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Grinder Operator**

Bremen Castings, Inc - Bremen, IN -

May 2018 to Present

Hand grinding an filling orders also operated grinding robot an some iron pouring

#### Hitch installer

U haul - South Bend, IN -

June 2017 to May 2018

Install hitches clean and park trucks interact with customers

## **Lawn Care Specialist**

TruGreen - South Bend, IN -

May 2017 to August 2017

Applied fertilizer to lawns responsible for the upkeep of customers grounds

## **Delivery Route Driver**

Home City Ice - Indianapolis, IN -

July 2016 to August 2016

Delivered ice daily and in a timely manner

# Sign installer

Lamar Advertising - Indianapolis, IN -

October 2015 to July 2016

Billboard hanging and installation, sign demolition and rebuild, some landscaping

#### Picker/Packer

PTG Logistics - Plainfield, IN -

September 2015 to September 2015

Picked packed and got ready for shipping

#### **Punchman**

The Tyler/ Letter9 - Indianapolis, IN -

July 2015 to August 2015

Responsibilities

Unit turns and trash outs general maintenance and some HVAC

Skills Used

Drywall hanging, carpentry, pluming...

# Formen/Helper

Master Movers LLC - Indianapolis, IN -

May 2015 to July 2015

Responsibilities

helped move other belongings one place to another and the paper work and payment of the job

#### Mower

New Wave Proporty Service - Zionsville, IN -

April 2015 to April 2015

Responsibilities

Mowing, Landscaping, Planting, Edging, Trimming, Sod laying

## Punchman

Cambridge Station - Indianapolis, IN -

June 2013 to August 2014

Maintenance

- Main office upkeep and cleaning
- Unit trash outs and make move in ready
- Work orders

Hallway porter

## **Crew member**

McDonald's - Indianapolis, IN -

March 2014 to June 2014

Food preperation

- Grill cook and cleaner
- Restaurant cleaning and upkeep

# **Security patrol**

Indianapolis Motor Speedway - Indianapolis, IN -

May 2013 to May 2013

# **Cashier/Customer Service**

Wesselman's - Evansville, IN -

September 2010 to August 2011

Cashier, stocker and product organizer

## **Lawn Care**

Turner and Son Landscping - South Bend, IN -

June 2009 to July 2009

Branch shrub and tree removal

- Grass cutting and yard care
- Hualing and trash clean up

**EDUCATION** 

## G.E.D.

Atterbury Job Corps - Edinburgh, IN

May 2011 to February 2012

SKILLS

Glazing (2 years)